Now I am going to show you how to do a triple buffalo.
Lift one foot up, strike the flat part of the toe tap on the floor, pull the flat part of the toe tap back, land on the ball of the foot.
Then you want to lift up the opposing foot, strike the flat part of that toe tap forward, pull the flat part of the tap back, hop and switch feet, remembering to land on the ball of your foot.
Lift the right foot, strike the flat part of the tap forward, pull the flat part of the tap back, land on the ball of the foot, strike the flat part of the opposing foot forward, pull the tap back, hop and switch feet.
Shuffle, step, shuffle, switch.
Now I am going to show you the side view of the triple buffalo.
Lift one foot, front, back, step, front, back, switch.
Now I am going to show you the rear view of the triple buffalo.
Shuffle, step, shuffle, switch.
Now I am going to show you how to travel with the triple buffalo.
The triple buffalo can be a very impressive way to change formations in your choreography.
Lift one foot, shuffle, step, shuffle, switch.
Shuffle, step, shuffle, switch.
Now I'll show you how to travel a little bit faster.
Now I'll show you the rear view traveling.
Shuffle, step, shuffle, hop.